<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All newsletter - Ziyi Liu</title>
        <link>https://ziiiliu.github.io/newsletter/</link>
        <description>All newsletter | Ziyi Liu</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://ziiiliu.github.io/newsletter/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Newsletter Issue 4</title>
    <link>https://ziiiliu.github.io/newsletter/issue4/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate><guid>https://ziiiliu.github.io/newsletter/issue4/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Intro Having embarked on two spontaneous short day-trips mostly due to the inspiration from the novel On the Road, I realised I share their trait of finding solace and peace in journeys, but I don&rsquo;t need to cross the whole continent multiple times just for that.
This week should be my last of buffer vacation between my conclusion of studies and my official commencement of working full time, so I can still have the luxury of enjoying a very diverse selection of reading.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Newsletter Issue 3</title>
    <link>https://ziiiliu.github.io/newsletter/issue3/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate><guid>https://ziiiliu.github.io/newsletter/issue3/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Intro This week of mine was filled by lethargy, and the high motivation level maintained since mid-June has seen its first major dip - sometimes I wonder how this correlates to the market. Maybe I should start using my mental energy level as a signal to backtest my yet-to-have investment strategy. However, when that signal looms near the bottom, my trading system/strategy will never deliver, so I will have to wait till it comes back up again to test this theory.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Newsletter Issue 2</title>
    <link>https://ziiiliu.github.io/newsletter/issue2/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate><guid>https://ziiiliu.github.io/newsletter/issue2/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Intro Hello again, welcome to the second issue of my newsletter. So yes, I have made it for the second consecutive week! And since this issue will be more flooded with my own comments and ideas than its predecessor, I will save you the trouble of reading through the formality of introduction - let&rsquo;s dive in!
Inbox Effective Altruism  I first came across the book 80,000 hours on my social media feed, thinking it&rsquo;s just another internet personality&rsquo;s ballyhoo; and I saw it again in my college library shortly after, so I couldn&rsquo;t help flipping through it to verify my hypothesis.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Newsletter Issue 1</title>
    <link>https://ziiiliu.github.io/newsletter/issue1/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 10:04:49 &#43;0000</pubDate><guid>https://ziiiliu.github.io/newsletter/issue1/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Intro Hi, I&rsquo;m Ziyi, and you are reading my very first newsletter. I&rsquo;ll be frank in the very beginning: I am not writing to cater to anyone&rsquo;s taste, and my biggest patron and vip subscriber is myself, which is exactly why I started this project.
Journaling has been a big hurdle in my entire life, despite my multiple attempts at it in different stages of life for vastly different reasons. In childhood, keeping a diary was a recurring homework for school, and as I was a rather absentminded and playful kid, not many events or thoughts really remain in my brain when I had to reluctantly pick up my pencil and rush a piece on Sunday night - so I made up some random stories.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
